http://www.julysoft.com/privacy-policy

PortalSaaS Login
Privacy PolicyINPHONITE PRIVACY STATEMENTInphonite is a software and cloud communication company. Your privacy is extremely important to us. We believe that to have integrity we must be thoughtful, honest and direct. In that spirit of transparency, this statement discloses the information practices for Inphonite websites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom exactly the information is shared.INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND SHARINGWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this or any Inphonite site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily submit. If at any time you prefer we do not use your information, you can opt-out by contacting us. We never have and never will sell or rent this information to anyone at any time for any reason and we will only use the information you give us for its intended purpose. Additionally, Inphonite will obtain appropriate protection if required to share information in any other way.We take precautions to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality online and offline. We use encryption and proper safeguards including security monitoring, to help us keep your information secure.COOKIES, WEB BEACONS, AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIESWe sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our ads or websites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we measure visitor activity on Inphonite websites. Inphonite or others on Inphonite's behalf may use non-identifiable data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner you can disable your cookies; if you do so, however, some pages may not work properly.DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAWPlease be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.LINKS TO NON-INPHONITE WEBSITESInphonite websites may contain links to other websites. Inphonite is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other websites.PRIVACY QUESTIONS AND ACCESSIf you have questions or concerns regarding your privacy or this Privacy Policy, contact Inphonite directly at 520-797-1844.
Inphonite, LLC
6367 E Tanque Verde Rd, Ste. 204,
Tucson, AZ 85715,
Follow us:
Copyright © 2020, Inphonite, LLC and/or its subsidiaries or affiliates. All Rights Reserved.
